Guide to the Ronald Reis photographs, 1954-2014 RL.01078
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1962-2014 and undated
  - Photographs and contact sheets, 1962-1979, 6 boxes
    - London: Hyde Park Speaker's Corner, 1964 Oct. (Box 4, Print rrph 10-1964E-21a)
    - New York City: Washington Square Park, 1964 Oct. (Box 4, Print rrph 10-1964E-24)
    - New York City: street scene [contact sheet], 1964 Oct. (Box 4, Print rrcs 10-1964F)
    - New York City: street scene after a parade, 1964 Oct. (Box 4, Print rrph 10-1964F-15a)
    - New York City: street scene after a parade, 1964 Oct. (Box 4, Print rrph 10-1964F-30a)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene [contact sheet], 1964 Nov. (Box 4, Print rrcs 11-1964D)
    - New Haven, CT: flea market, 1964 Nov. (Box 4, Print rrph 11-1964D-15a)
    - New Haven, CT: flea market, 1964 Nov. (Box 4, Print rrph 11-1964D-25)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene [contact sheet], 1964 Nov. (Box 4, Print rrcs 11-1964E)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene, 1964 Nov. (Box 4, Print rrph 11-1964E-31a)
    - New Haven, CT: Firemen at house fire [contact sheet], 1964 Dec. (Box 4, Print rrcs 12-1964G)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene, 1964 Dec. (Box 4, Print rrph 12-1964G-18a)
    - New York City: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Jan. (Box 4, Print rrcs 01-1965B)
    - New York City: street scene, 1965 Jan. (Box 4, Print rrph 01-1965B-4a)
    - New York City: street scene, 1965 Jan. (Box 4, Print rrph 01-1965B-9a)
    - New York City: street scene, 1965 Jan. (Box 4, Print rrph 01-1965B-34a)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Jan. (Box 4, Print rrcs 01-1965C)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene, 1965 Jan. (Box 4, Print rrph 01-1965C-8a)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Feb. (Box 4, Print rrcs 02-1965D)
    - New Haven, CT: "the Green", 1965 Feb. (Box 4, Print rrph 02-1965D-18a)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Feb. (Box 4, Print rrcs 02-1965E)
    - New Haven, CT: "the Green", 1965 Feb. (Box 4, Print rrph 02-1965E-00)
    - New Haven, CT: "the Green", 1965 Feb. (Box 4, Print rrph 02-1965E-8a)
    - New York City: St. Patrick's Day Parade [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrcs 03-1965D)
    - New York City: St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965D-14a)
    - New York City: St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965D-20a)
    - London: Hyde Park Speaker's Corner [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrcs 03-1965H)
    - London: Hyde Park Speaker's Corner, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965H-12)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrcs 03-1965J)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965J-2a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965J-27a)
    - New York City: St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965-00)
    - London: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrcs 03-1965L)
    - London: Antique shop, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965L-7a)
    - London: school boys on Regent Street, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965L-20a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965L-29a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965L-31a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrcs 03-1965M)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965M-8)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965M-10)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965M-26)
    - London: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrcs 03-1965N)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965N-4a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965N-14a)
    - London: Hyde Park Speaker's Corner, 1965 Mar. (Box 4, Print rrph 03-1965N-32a)
    - London: street scene [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 5, Print rrcs 03-1965O)
    - London: street musicians, 1965 Mar. (Box 5, Print rrph 03-1965O-3a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market [contact sheet], 1965 Mar. (Box 5, Print rrcs 03-1965R)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1965 Mar. (Box 5, Print rrph 03-1965R-27a)
    - New York City: Greenwich Village [contact sheet], 1965 Sept. (Box 5, Print rrcs 09-1965A)
    - New York City: Greenwich Village, 1965 Sept. (Box 5, Print rrph 09-1965A-7a)
    - New York City: Greenwich Village, 1965 Sept. (Box 5, Print rrph 09-1965A-12a)
    - Athens: street scene [contact sheet], 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1967E)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967E-8a)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967E-32a)
    - Spain: street scene [contact sheet], 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1967F)
    - Barcelona: Ritz Hotel, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967F-10a)
    - Barcelona: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967F-15a)
    - Barcelona: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967F-23a)
    - Greece: street scene [contact sheet], 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1967G)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967G-14a)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967G-28a)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967G-33a)
    - Athens: street scene [contact sheet], 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1967H)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967H-5)
    - Athens: street scene [contact sheet], 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1967K)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967K-16a)
    - Athens: street scene, 1967 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1967K-28a)
    - London: street scene [contact sheet], 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1968C)
    - London: street musician, 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1968C-26a)
    - London: street scene [contact sheet], 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1968D)
    - London: Hyde Park Speaker's Corner, 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1968D-31a)
    - London: street scene [contact sheet], 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrcs 04-1968E)
    - London: street scene, 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1968E-7a)
    - London: street scene, 1968 Apr. (Box 5, Print rrph 04-1968E-9a)
    - London: Portobello Road flea market, 1969 July (Box 5, Print rrph 07-1969-x1)
    - London: street scene, 1969 July (Box 5, Print rrph 07-1969-x2)
    - London: Trafalgar Square, 1969 July (Box 5, Print rrph 07-1969-x3)
    - Philadelphia: North Philadelphia, sitting on front stoop, 1950-1959 (Box 5, Print rrph 1950s-x1)
    - New York City: Bryant Park, Biafra demonstration, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Print rrph 1960s-x1)
    - New York City: New York Public Library at 42nd Street, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Print rrph 1960s-x2)
    - Queens, NY: TWA Terminal at Idlewild Airport (JFK), 1963 (Box 5, Print rrph 1963-x1)
    - New Haven, CT: flea market [contact sheet], 1971 Sept. (Box 6, Print rrcs 09-1971J)
    - New Haven, CT: flea market, 1971 Sept. (Box 6, Print rrph 09-1971J-8a)
    - New Haven, CT: flea market, 1971 Sept. (Box 6, Print rrph 09-1971J-22a)
    - New Haven, CT: flea market, 1971 Sept. (Box 6, Print rrph 09-1971J-25a)
    - Jerusalem: market scenes [contact sheet], 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrcs 08-1972A)
    - Jerusalem: market in the old city, 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrph 08-1972A-0)
    - Jerusalem: market in the old city, 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrph 08-1972A-19)
    - Jerusalem: market in the old city, 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrph 08-1972A-20)
    - Jerusalem: street scene [contact sheet], 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrcs 08-1972B)
    - Jerusalem: market in the old city, 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrph 08-1972B-6a)
    - Jerusalem: Mea Shaarim, 1972 Aug. (Box 6, Print rrph 08-1972B-19a)
    - New Haven, CT: street scene, 1973 Nov. (Box 6, Print rrph 11-1973-x1)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x1)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x2)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x3)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x4)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x5)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x6)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x7)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x8)
    - New York City: anti-Vietnam war demonstration in Bryant Park., 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x9)
    - London: Beauchamp Place, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x10)
    - London: street scene, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x11)
    - London: Beauchamp Place, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x12)
    - London: Beauchamp Place, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x13)
    - London: Beauchamp Place, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x14)
    - London: street scene, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x15)
    - London: street scene, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Print rrph 1970s-x16)
  - Photographs, 2004-2014 and undated
    This later body of work consists of over 3500 digital inkjet prints, both black-and-white and color, the majority of which measure 11x17 inches and are printed on Ilford Galerie Smooth Pearl 290gsm paper. They are arranged roughly in order of geographical location, with original group titles as assigned by Reis. Subjects focus on New York City street scenes, but there are also images from other states Reis visited in New England and in western U.S. (Colorado); there is also a set of images taken in Canada.
    - New York City; East Haven, CT: street scenes: Latino protest -Black and white, color, 2005-2012; 33 photographs (Box 9)
    - New York City; Harvard Square, Cambridge, MA: sreet scenes -Color, 2008, 2011, 2012; 43 photographs (Box 9)
    - Denver, CO; South Bend, IN: Street scenes -Color, September 2003, April 2010, July 2012, November 2012; 35 photographs (Box 9)
    - New York City: street scenes: San Gennaro Festival, Lexington Avenue Street Fair -Color, September 2011; 52 photographs (Box 9)
    - New York City: street scenes: Highline, Steve Jobs Memorial, Eldridge Street Fair -Color, May, June, October 2011; 44 photographs (Box 9)
    - New York City; New Haven, CT: street scenes: Wall Street protestors, NYC Marathon -Color, 2011; 39 photographs (Box 10)
    - New York City; Branford, CT: street scenes: Newport boat show -Color, August 2009 to September 2011, January 2012, and undated; 31 photographs (Box 10)
    - New York City: street scenes: Chinese New Year Parade, South Street Seaport -Color, January 2012; 44 photographs (Box 10)
    - New York City: street scenes: St. Patrick's Day, Central Park, Cops, Starbucks -Color, March 2012; 46 photographs (Box 10)
    - New York City: street scenes -Color, May 2012; 42 photographs (Box 10)
    - New York City: street scenes: 3rd Avenue Street Fair, Times Square -Color, May, June 2012; 45 photographs (Box 11)
    - New York City: parks, June, July 2012; 36 photographs (Box 11)
    - New York City: street scenes: Madison Avenue Street Fair, 44 photographs (Box 11)
    - New York City; Boston, MA: street scenes: Massachusetts Museum of Contemporary Art -Color, July, October 2012; 50 photographs (Box 11)
    - New York City; Boston, MA; Denver, CO: street scenes: Denver Art Musuem: "Myself", July 2005, August 2005, May 2008, August 2012, December 2012; 40 photographs (Box 11)
    - New York City: street scenes: Union Square, Metro North Trains, 5th Avenue, 72nd Street -Black and white, October, November 2012; 45 photographs (Box 12)
    - New York City: street scenes: -Black and white, November 2012; 42 photographs (Box 12)
    - New York City: street scenes, Batya's Bat Mitzvah -Black and white, December 2012; 47 photographs (Box 12)
    - New York City, street scenes -Black and white, color, December 2012; 54 photographs (Box 12)
    - New York City: street scenes -Color, 2004, 2012, and undated; 48 photographs (Box 12)
    - New York City: street scenes -Black and white, January 2013; 61 photographs (Box 13)
    - New York City: street scenes: Central Park -Black and white, January-April 2013; 45 photographs (Box 13)
    - New York City: street scenes: Union Square, "Freedom Tower," 3rd Avenue Street Fair, Washington Square, Upper West Side, Times Square -Black and white, May-June 2013; 57 photographs (Box 13)
    - New York City; Portland, ME: Street scenes, Rooftops -Black and white, color, June 2013; 56 photographs (Box 13)
    - New York City: street scenes: Central Park, Lexington Avenue -Black and white, June, July 2013; 28 photographs (Box 13)
    - New York City: street scenes: Central Park, Upper East Side, Apple store area -Black and white, color, July 2013; 59 photographs (Box 14)
    - New York City: street scenes -Black and white, March-April 2013; 83 photographs (Box 14)
    - New York City: street scenes -Black and white, color, May 2013; 56 photographs (Box 14)
    - New York City: street scenes: Washington Square, Lincoln Center, Times Square, Upper West Side, June 2013; 77 photographs (Box 14)
    - New York City; Branford, CT: street scenes -Black and white, color, September 2013; 59 photographs (Box 15)
    - New York City; Northampton, MA; Wilmington, VT: street scenes, trips -Black and white, color, June-July 2013; 34 photographs (Box 15)
    - New York City: street scenes: Lexington Avenue Fair, Union Square, Lower East Side -Black and white, color, August 2013; 54 photographs (Box 15)
    - New York City: street scenes -Black and white, August 2013; 67 photographs (Box 15)
    - New York City: street scenes: Brazilian Day Street Festival -Black and white, color, September 2013; 44 photographs (Box 15)
    - New York City: street scenes: CBGB Festival, Hispanic Day Parade -Black and white, color, October-November 2013; 39 photographs (Box 16)
    - New York City: street scenes: Union Square, Plaza Hotel -Black and white, color, December 2013; 68 photographs (Box 16)
    - New York City: street scenes: Oxford view, Union Square, Columbus Circle, train views, Plaza Hotel area -Black and white, color, December 2013, January 2014; 66 photographs (Box 16)
    - New York City; New Haven, CT: street scenes: Oxford views, Union Square, winter storm, January 2014; 68 photographs (Box 16)
    - New York City: street scenes: Chinatown, restaurant scenes, February 2014; 62 photographs (Box 17)
    - New York City: street scenes: Union Square, interior of Time Warner building -Black and white, February-March 2014; 67 photographs (Box 17)
    - New York City: street scenes: Times Square -Black and white, color, April 2014; 75 photographs (Box 17)
    - New York City: street scenes: Upper West Side -Black and white, color, 31 photographs (Box 17)
    - New York City: street scenes -Black and white, color, April 2014; 54 photographs (Box 18)
    - New York City; Newport, RI: street scenes -Black and white, color, various dates; 34 photographs (Box 18)
    - Camden, Portland, Rockland, Northeast Harbor, Southwest Harbor, ME; David and Donna's camp, September 2012; 31 photographs (Box 18)
    - St. Louis, MO; Chicago, IL; Clarion, PA; Harrisburg, PA; Bentonville, AR -color, September 2012; 73 photographs (Box 18)
    - Branford, CT; New Haven, CT -Black and white, color, June 2012; 41 photographs (Box 18)
    - Chapel Hill, NC; Greensboro, NC; Fredericksburg, VA; Alexandria, VA; Philadelphia, PA -Black and white, color, 71 photographs (Box 19)
    - Washington, DC; Chapel Hill, NC; Durham, NC; Hillborough, NC; Raleigh, NC; Baltimore, MD -Black and white, color, March 2013; 55 photographs (Box 19)
    - New York City: Lower Manhattan, Miscellaneous Street Scenes - Color, June, July 2012; 32 photographs (Box 20)
    - Gay Pride; Harvard Visit; Miscellaneous Color - Black and white, color, 2008-2011; 31 photographs (Box 20)
    - Newport Boat Show - Color, September 2013; 59 photographs (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous New York City street scenes; Gay Pride Parade - Color, June 2012; 38 photographs (Box 20)
    - Metronorth train station - Black and white, color, 2013-2014; 34 photographs (Box 20)
    - Mexican Day Parade (New York City) - Color, September 2012; 26 photographs (Box 20)
    - New York City: street scenes, new condo building, streets and Upper Westside - Black and white, color, April 2014; 29 photographs (Box 20)
    - New York City: street scenes, Central Park - Black and white, color, September 2013; 21 photographs (Box 21)
    - New York City: Washington Square Area, street scenes - Black and white, color, October 2013; 33 photographs (Box 21)
    - Contact prints from: Toshiba laptop: Picasa starred photos, serious pics I and II, Nudes and Other Naked Ladies; Mac Laptop: iPhoto starred photos - Black and white, color; Joe and Heidi wedding dances - Black and white, color, November 2011, April 2012; 26 photographs (Box 21)
    - Veteran's Day Parade (Branford, East Haven) - Black and white, November 2012; 34 photographs (Box 21)
    - New York City: San Gennaro Festival, China Town, street scenes - Black and white, color, September 2013; 37 photographs (Box 21)
    - New York City: street scenes, South St. Seaport, Halloween décor - Black and white, color, October 2013; 32 photographs (Box 21)
    - Trip to Maine; New York City: street scenes, Bryant Park - Color, Black and white, October, November 2013; 28 photographs (Box 21)
    - New York City: Madison Ave Fair, Union Square, street scenes - Black and white, November 2013; 32 photographs (Box 21)
    - New York City: Union Square, Upper Westside, street scenes - Black and white, November 2013; 27 photographs (Box 22)
    - Occupy Wall Street; miscellaneous New York City street scenes; Starbucks people - Color, September, October 2012; 48 photographs (Box 22)
    - New York City: Washington Square, Greenwich Village, street scenes - Black and white, July 2013; 34 photographs (Box 22)
    - Muslim Day Parade (New York City) - Black and white, September 2013; 26 photographs (Box 22)
    - New York City: South Street Area, Wall Street Area, street scenes,Times Square - Black and white, color, August 2013; 34 photographs (Box 22)
    - Trip to Canada; miscellaneous - Color, July 2011; 43 photographs (Box 22)
    - Cops (at Columbus Day Parade), miscellaneous New York City street scenes and earlier, Annapolis, Maryland - Color; New York City miscellaneous (including Can Men), April 2003, October 2012; 28 photographs (Box 22)
    - New York City: Street Scenes, Central Park, Greek Day Parade, Union Square, GCT; Cambridge, Massachusetts - Black and white, color, April 2013; 46 photographs (Box 23)
    - Trip to Charleston, South Carolina; Stops at: Chapel Hill, North Carolina, Alexandria, Virginia, Georgetown, Raleigh, North Carolina - Color, February 2012; 36 photographs (Box 23)
    - Cops, firemen - Black and white, color, 2012-2013; 42 photographs (Box 23)
    - Cops, firemen - Black and white, color, 2013-2014; 21 photographs (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous - Black and white, color, 2004-2005; 28 photographs (Box 23)
    - Cops - Black and white, color, 2006-2012 and undated; 50 photographs (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous; Can man - Black and white, color, March 2004, 2009; 4 photographs (Box 23)
    - Metronorth - Black and white, color, 2012-2013; 2 folders (Box 24)
      93 photographs
    - Miscellaneous - Black and white, color, 2003-2013; 4 folders (Box 24)
      128 photographs
    - Winter storm, January 2014; 1 photographs (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous digital prints - Black and white, color, 2011, 2012, undated; 35 photographs (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous digital prints - Black and white, color, 2011, 2012, and undated; 29 photographs (Box 25)
- Negatives, 1954-1976 and undated
  Series contains 66 envelopes containing 35 mm negatives and 13 envelopes of 120 mm negatives; each envelope holds one roll of film cut into strips. Images correspond to locales of prints in the collection, including Connecticut, Pennsylvania, New York City, and various countries in Europe, especially England (London), Greece, and Italy. There are also images from a trip to Jerusalem in the 1970s. Also among the images are Vietnam protest marches and other demonstrations, as well as early street scenes from urban areas and shots taken at an amusement park in Connecticut, "Savin Rock."
  The negatives are arranged chronologically by year and month, and within by location and strip letter id, with undated items at the end of the series. Titles are taken from notes on the original envelopes. Some negatives represent images not currently among the prints or contact sheets.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Negatives are closed to use. Corresponding prints may be available in the collection; otherwise, reproduction copies may be requested.
  Please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use these materials.
  - 1954, Black kids playing -- streets of Philadelphia, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 June, West Haven, CT, Strip G, Savin Rock, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 August, New York City, Strip L, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 August, Strip G, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 August, Strip M, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 September, West Haven, CT, Strip D, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 September, New York City, Strip C, Greenwich Village, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 October, Strip C, Philadelphia reunion, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1962 November, Strip R, Clown at Savin Rock fun house, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 January, Strip B, Nuns--never printed, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 February, Strip F, Overturned row boat in snow, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 March, London, Strip E, Hyde Park, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 March, London, Strip G, Hyde Park, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 March, London, Strip H, Hyde Park, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 March, London, Strip J, London scenes, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 March, London, Strip K, London scenes, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 March, Strip A, Newspaper man in kiosk, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 May, Strip D, Dr. Bill Kessler, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 June, New York City, Strip F, NYC cops / Parade crowds, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 June, New York City, Strip J, NYC street scenes, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 June, New York City, Strip K, NYC street scenes, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 June, New York City, Strip L, NYC street scenes, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 June, St. Louis, MO, Strip N, Park scenes including "Woman and Duck", 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 July, New York City (Washington Square), Strip B; Couple resting on edge of fountain; single negative: man asleep in front of store, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 August, New York City, Strip H, NYC street scenes, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 September, Strip B, John and Peter Resnick, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 October, Danbury, CT, Strip B, Danbury Fair, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 October, Danbury, CT, Strip C, Danbury Fair, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 October, New York City, Strip A; Fashion shots; 3 NYC street scenes, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 October, Strip G, Savin Rock, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 October, Strip H, Savin Rock, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1963 October, Strip J, Savin Rock, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 April, Florence--Rome, Strip C, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 April, Florence, Strip D, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 April, Florence, Strip E, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 April, Florence--Venice, Strip F, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 April, London, Strip K, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 April, Rome, Strip A, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 July, New York City, Strip D, NYC street scenes (several in show), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 September, New York City, Strip D, Greenwich Village, 35 mm (Box 8)